#### Contact

5016970909 (Mobile) jrlemon07@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jayme-lemon-043235112 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

**Nursing Management** 

Nursing

Hospitals

### Certifications

**ACLS** 

Advanced Stroke Life Support (ASLS)

BLS

Certified Lean & Six Sigma Green Belt (CLSSGB)

Certified Medical Surgical Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

### Honors-Awards

DAISY Award for Extraordinary Nurses

40 Nurse Leaders Under 40

# Jayme Lemon

MSN, RN, CMSRN, SCRN, CLSSGB

Conway, Arkansas

# Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care setting including assistance of opening a 111 bed acute care hospital.

Skilled in Nursing Management, Nursing, Inpatient Care, Hospitals, Clinical Risk Management, and Healthcare. Strong professional with a Master of Science (MSN) focused in Nursing Administration and Leadership. Nationally certified in Medical/Surgical nursing, Stroke, and Lean Six Sigma.

# Experience

**Baptist Health** 

8 years 1 month

Risk Manager/Patient Safety Officer June 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Registered Nurse Supervisor October 2015 - June 2018 (2 years 9 months) Conway, AR

Manager of an 8 bed ICU/CCU and the In-House Agency/Flex Team at Baptist Heath Medical Center - Conway.

Administrative RN III April 2015 - October 2015 (7 months)

Registered Nurse

June 2012 - April 2015 (2 years 11 months)

Little Rock, Arkansas Area

## Education

Western Governors University

Master of Science (MS), Nursing Administration · (2016 - 2018)

Page 1 of 2

The University of Texas at Arlington
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2013 - 2015)

Rasmussen College
Associate of Science (A.S.), Nursing · (2010 - 2012)

Pasco-Hernando State College Associate of Arts (A.A.), Undergrad · (2009 - 2010)

University of Central Arkansas Undergrad · (2007 - 2009)